Rolando Mora Cordero

Software Developer

Holder of a diploma in Information Technologies, certified as a Cloud Practitioner by AWS and currently pursuing a degree in Computer Engineering at Tecnológico of Costa Rica. Possesses work experience in UI development, freelance work, and IT support.

 $\frac{rolandomorac@gmail.com}{934a67215} \cdot \frac{(+506)8680\ 0570}{954a67215} \cdot \frac{linkedin.com/in/rolando-mora-cordero-linkedin.com/Rolando1010}{954a67215} \cdot \frac{(+506)8680\ 0570}{954a67215} \cdot \frac{linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/linkedin.com/$

Experience

IT Support at Namu Travel Group (August 2022 – December 2022)

- Support to the problems of the internal systems of the company.
- Analysis, debugging and development with legacy code.
- Implementation of agile methodologies like SCRUM and JIRA.

Freelance in Web application development (January 2022 - May 2022)

- Web application developed in Django and React, with different user roles and access levels, statistical graphics generation, PDF reports, file storage in cloud, real time notifications, automated data backup, photographs and videos capturing, work chronograms, authentication and data extraction from excel.
- API REST creation in Django using the integrated ORM, together with a MYSQL remote database access and using an AWS messaging system.

University intern at Dinámica Consultores (September 2022 – December 2022)

- User experience improvements in UI of a web application oriented to project management.
- Contribution of various proposals for reporting with statistical graphics, along with a proof of concept that implemented such libraries.

Education

- Computing Engineering at Tecnólogico of Costa Rica (2021 Now)
- AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner at Amazon Web Services (2023 January)
- Information technologies diplomate at Cartago University College (CUC) (2019 2020)

Knowledge

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Python
- C#
- Java
- C++

- React
- NextJS
- CSS
- NodeJS
- Django

- Flask
- .NET
- MongoDB
- SQLServer
- PostgreSQL

Languages

- Spanish (Native)
- English (B1 B2)